大家好！我是叶修,
Hello everyone! My name is YeXiu.
你们可以叫我叶老师！
You can call me Mr.Ye
欢迎来到我英文课程。
Welcome to my English class!
我们会在这堂课说英文。
We'll speak English in my class.
英文是我的母语，
English is my first language,
所以无论你在英文学习的哪个阶段，我都可以教！
so whatever your English level is, I can teach you!
那如果你以前从未学过英文,
If you've never learnt English before,
而且不明白我在说什么，没事，
and have trouble understanding me, no worries,
我可以和你说中文。
I can speak Chinese with you.
但是我才学中文一年，
Although I've only been learning Chinese for a year,
所以希望我们之间尽量说英文!
so my hope is that we can speak English to each other.
我觉得学习语言的最好方法是学习一个国家的文化，
I think the best way to learn a language is to learn about the culture that the language comes from.
所以，在我的课上，你可以了解到北美文化。
so, in my class, you can learn about North American culture.
如果你已经有一本英文书,
If you already have an English textbook to learn from,
我可以帮助你解决书上的问题!
I can help you understand your course's material.
那接下来，让我们一起学英文吧!
Now, let's learn English together!
And if you're not a Chinese speaker, that's totally fine.
如果你不会说中文，那也没关系。
My name is Brad, and I come from Vancouver, Canada.
我叫Brad，来自加拿大温哥华。
And as someone who's already learning a second language, I understand how hard it can be.
作为一个已经在学习第二语言的人，我能理解其中的困难。
To understand people when they talk too fast
当人们说话太快时如何理解，
or understand how to read efficiently
或者如何高效阅读，
or understand how to speak with decent pronunciation.
或者如何做到优秀的发音。
But in my class, I want to go at the speed of the student.
但是在我的课堂上，我想以学生可接受的速度进行。
And so if you feel that you're not understanding a study question or a certain topic,
所以如果你觉得不理解某个问题或某个主题，
we won't move on until you do.
我们会直到你理解再继续。
And I want to be available to my students.
我希望更好地服务学生，
And so once we're in class, I'll be happy to give you my WhatsApp.
所以上课时，我会告诉你们我的WhatsApp。
And anytime you have questions about homework or anything English related,
如果你有任何关于作业或任何英语相关的问题，
feel free to message me, and I'll get right back to you.
请随时给我发信息 ，我会尽快回复。
I'm more than excited to help you on your English journey, and I'll see you in class.
我非常高兴能在你的英语之旅中帮助你，我们课上见！